Anders Splawinski

425-422-8339

Email: asplawinski@protonmail.com

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/anders-splawinski-83a74359/

About me: After initially getting involved in computer repair in high school Anders has gone on to receive multiple certifications in Information Technology related subjects. He has pursued an associates degree in Information Technology and completed nearly 95% of the required credits to graduate. After receiving a one year certification for Computer Support specialist from his college Anders went on to work in a high volume service desk position where he received excellent feedback from customers and co-workers alike. After spending nearly a year at this position he's ready to move on to the next challenge.

Certs

CompTIA A+

Code: LTSTZ56P53R4QDKH Verify at: http://verify.CompTIA.org

CompTIA Security+

Code: PT29QMXF7P1Q1KS9 Verify at: http://verify.CompTIA.org

CompTIA IT Fundamentals

Code: ZR6S7L0FQDRQQ1GZ Verify at: http://verify.CompTIA.org

- Computer Support Specialist Certification from EVCC
- Microsoft MTA

Microsoft MTA Security Fundamentals

Microsoft MTA Network Fundamentals

Microsoft MTA Windows Operating System Fundamentals

Skills

- Hands-on experience repairing a wide variety of laptop and desktop computers/components including printers and mobile phones.
- Great communication and customer service skills.
- Security, best practices, and implementation.
- Active directory.
- Comfortable in Linux systems as well as Windows.
- Familiar with and can execute/interpret bash, powershell, ruby, php, and other languages.
- PXE deployment/Windows image creation and deployment, WDS.
- Virtual machine deployment and management/VMware, vSphere, Virtual Box.
- Networking/Cisco router and switch management including network design, vlans, and Cisco CLI.
- Excellent with multitasking and customer service oriented workflow.

Experience

Tek Systems - IT service desk technician

2021-2022

Worked in a high volume IT service center at Boeing everett where he supported 1000's of customers.

Tasked with diagnosing, repairing, and communicating with customers about their computers.

Extensive laptop break fix and software troubleshooting.

F1 consultancy- Technical Consultant

2018 - 2020 (intermittent)

- Set up, deployed, and maintained physical network infrastructure in a large fast paced dynamic tech convention environment.
- Tasked with both troubleshooting IT issues for presenters and physical deployment/upkeep of hardware to the many rooms.
- Customer focused duties included taking calls and emails for technical assistance with a variety of hardware and issues during the shows and documenting problems for escalation if need be.
- Maintained a professional presence and demeanor working among thousands of employees in Microsoft's many conventions held all over the country.

Lab Tech- Tech/Student Help desk at EVCC

2019 - 2019 (6 months)

- Assisted with issues and problems arising with the Cisco networking equipment.
- Worked with a large group of students taking questions and emails about issues as well as teaching various Cisco networking lessons to students in a one on one setting.
- Developed a deep knowledge of networking and Cisco equipment.

Education

Everett Community College (EVCC)

2018-2020 (Currently one semester from associates)

Computer Support Specialist Certification

Projects & Organizations

 My main personal project at the moment consists of a purposefully vulnerable LAMP stack with a multitude of pentesting labs and activities like SQLI labs, bWAPP, and DVWA. While at EVCC Anders helped run our ethical hacking club as its vice president. He helped to organize learning opportunities and worked with a group of great IT students and professionals with the goal of furthering knowledge of security and pentesting.

Customer service experience

Target - Electronic sales clerk.

2015-2017

Fred Meyer- Electronic sales clerk/supervisor

2008-2014

- Customer service/sales oriented role in the retail electronics departments.
- Excellent customer service cultivated in a long retail career.
- Met the needs of many individuals helping them find the best solutions to their electronic needs.
- Explained devices and technology to a large variety of people and age groups in a way that made sense.
- Often took high volumes of calls while providing customer assistance during seasonal rushes and sales.